Nogizaka Morning
Don! Here we go!
Nogizaka Contusi
I'm your host, Bananaman.
I'm Bananaman, your host.
I'm Nogizaka, and I'll be right with you.
Yay!
Seino
No chairs today
I got a project to do today.
Please do it.
Nogizaka Kong Master
Nogizaka46 will soon celebrate its 11th anniversary.
Nogizaka46 will soon celebrate its 11th anniversary with more than 250 songs.
So this time, I'd like to share with you
This time, we're going to quiz you on the songs that the members of Nogizaka46 should know.
This is a quiz that cuts through the songs from various angles.
The members are chosen by themselves.
and Bananaman, who is well-known as a member of the team, will participate as a team of two.
The one who earns the most points
will be certified as Nogizaka Song Master!
There is a very good chance that we will be the song master
We are very likely to become Song Masters.
We are going to get the Nogizaka Song Master.
So, this time, we're going to ask you to do a few things.
Over there, right?
That's right.
We four will be selected as the Nogizaka Song Selection.
Song Selection is a cool selection.
If we go to that side, we'll be overwhelmed.
Kubo is strong, but the other members are not.
Kubo was strong, but the other members were strong.
It was something.
Kubo's absence is a good thing.
You don't know Hayashi.
He's hard-hitting.
You know him?
Yes, I know him.
You know him? You know Tamura?
Yes, I know.
I'd look like an idiot if I went there.
You really don't know anything about Sakaguchi either, do you?
I know.
He's not allowed to say anything other than "I know.
Kubo's a musician and a great actress.
Thank you very much.
That's great!
She's going to play Ieyasu.
No, no, no...
No, no, no... you surprised me.
No, it's not.
But we're rivals because we're both gourmets behind the scenes.
That's right.
Look at "Sekkkaku Gourmet.
Yes, we're the same.
With the TV on.
With the channel on.
You're not going to turn off the channel?
If you turn off the channel, it means the channel starts when you die.
That's right.
Guess the clue! What song?
First of all, you will take a quiz to guess the name of the song from various clues given by the music selection committee. 10 points will be given if you can answer the first clue.
The faster you can answer the question, the more points you will get.
You will make your announcement in a state of invisibility and never raise your voice until I give you the signal.
Next time, when Mamba goes, that song will be erased more and more.
The first clue is the picture.
If you guess the picture alone, you will get 10 points, so I hope you will do your best.
It's a picture of a bad guy, a picture drawn by a bad guy!
What kind of illustration will Sakaguchi use to express the song?
Then, please give us a hint.
Let's see if you've got it.
What's this?
It's a quick press, everyone!
May I ask you all to keep your faces down?
Let's see your faces, please.
What a pain in the ass!
I have no idea.
You've been keeping your face down for a long time.
I pressed it.
Yes, sir.
Too bad.
One more time.
Let me see A one more time.
I'm sure.
What's this? Is it a face?
Is it a face?
Oh, no...
Okay, I read it. Go ahead.
Go ahead, Ayame.
Is it over?
Last call, Himura-san.
Can I go?
If there had been any giggles, we'd have all been singing the same song.Good, because if there was any giggling going on, we'd all be out of the same song.
I see... with that picture.
They're all the same song, like, five times in a row.
Really?
I'm surprised.
I guess we didn't all get the first one.
Wait a minute... you've been face down for so long, I can't see your face.
I can't see the picture.
The humming three notes cut out of a piece of music from the second clue.
I'm pretty sure I don't know the humming.
I'm sure it'll come into focus as soon as you figure it out.
Then give me a clue, please.
Whew!
Please answer, everyone!
Some of you might be able to see it.
Let's guess with just three syllables.
Excuse me.
Which one is this?
That's the clue that you don't know.
Congratulations!
You've done it!
Come in, Mr. Yura.
I'm confident.
Wrong.
Who's that? Yuna, please throw away your face.
Too bad.
Guess who, Mr. Kitahara?
No, you didn't.
No, no, no...
Ms. Manatsu!
No, it's not.
I'd like to hear it one more time.
If you know what follows...
I'm sure.
Yuna.
No.
It doesn't hit me. I wonder what it is.
It won't hit me.
Mr. Sapporo, shall we go last?
What?
No?
That's the end of the second clue.
It's too hard!
This is the hardest quiz I've ever done!
It's so hard!
I'll let you guess next time.
The third clue is A-bread!
Kubo chose
King!
Everyone please keep your face down!
Correct answer
What did you guess?
It's over.
I don't even know what I guessed.
I can't even rejoice.
I wish you'd already guessed this one, Kaki.
It's out of focus.
Eh.
The correct answer was you scolded me.
eh?
From the pose of the crown.
I guessed it first.
Correct.
Because of the crown pose?
The choreography is impressive, isn't it?
But then again, so is Sakaguchi's painting.
That's true.
I want to see the painting.
There's a light on his head.
Oh, I got scolded.
Oh...
Where is the humming part?
The beginning of the A melody.
That's where she's singing.
The humming...
Oh.
It's difficult.
The first clue to the second question is in the expression on your face.
I don't know if I can tell by the expression on your face.
That's a big one.
How does Tamura express it by facial expression alone?
Then, please give us a hint.
No, no, no...
What's this?
What?
It's cute.
Very good!
Plum blossoms!
No?
No, it's not.
It's different.
Midsummer.
Here you go.
No, it's not.
Oh, very...
Nyan-chan
Here you go.
I made a mistake.I made a little mistake.
I'm sorry.
Ayane, come in.
No, it's not.
I read it.
Here you go.
It's similar to the nuance.
Yumitsu!
Two people who might win, please.
The second one.
What the hell?
This is too hard!
What's more, I want to see other people's work!
It's amazing how everyone was able to get the same nuance of what I was trying to say.
I think you hit the nail on the head.
You were right.
The next clue is an English word.
I think a lot of people can do that.
Then, please give us a hint.
Please write it down.
What? What is it?
It's a quick press, sir.
My index finger's gone bad.
Please keep your faces down, ladies and gentlemen.
Young man?
I made a mistake.
Waka-ko.
Ayame.
I made a mistake.
They wanted one of us to leave.
Yamashita, please.
Oh, you're right, it's not.
It's getting away from my expression.
You should remember the expression on your brow.
So far, I haven't come up with the right answer.
Based on the two clues...
The third clue is
Kubo humming 3 amps
Mm-hm-hm-hm
Oops.
Eh, I don't know anymore.
Everyone keep your face down, please.
Plum blossoms, please.
I'm sorry, no.
Staff.
Oh, no.
No, you're not.
Yumiki.
Too bad.
Staff.
What's this?
I'm sorry. No, sir.
I'll take a look at this.
No, sir.
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Not at all.
Ayane.
Correct.
What do you mean?
The correct answer was romantic ikayaki.
Ah!
Ikaringu?
I was thinking...
Ikaringu.
You're going to say "hmmm" or something?
Not at all.
There it is.
What's that first expression?
It's a romantic expression.
I don't get it.
This is hard, but I'll be happy if I guess it.
I'm so disappointed...
I'm so frustrated!
After this, a series of miracle answers!
YUMESAN!
I'm going to make a slight change to the rules for the new quiz in the state of "Decisive Action".
If you get the right answer, we're done. The first clue for the third question is Hayashi's expression.
I'd like to take a picture of him with the right expression.
Please give me a hint.
Good!
What? Good?
What? What is it?
I'm sorry.
Expression
Ayame.
No, no, no, I thought I got it.
Here it is.
Correct!
Yes!
You're kidding! I got it!
10 points! How did you do that?
That's amazing!
That's Asuka's expression, isn't it?
That's right!
I get it!
It's so similar!
That's what I'm talking about!
The last one you often do at live shows.
The last one!Last one!
Asuka looking embarrassed.
Oh, man, I'm never gonna get this off.
It'll feel so good when I get it.
Ten points here?
Ten points here? !
Wow!
It's huge!
The fourth question is a brand-new item, expressed with a single kanji character.
Beautiful
beautiful
Oh!
Kitahara-san
Ah, congratulations!
I wouldn't do that.
This is impossible, isn't it?
It's not.
Plum, please.
Sorry about the plums.
Here you go, Yuna.
No, it's not.
Beauty...
Beauty is what you think is beautiful.
What do you think is beautiful?
Beauty, Ayase!
Spray to clean.
No, it's not.
Because it's clean or because it's cleaning?
The correct answer is in kanji!
Next is Gaja-kun again!
Is it a picture or a slice of bread?
A picture. How difficult...
I guess I just have to understand.
Then, please give us a hint.
Eh, good.
He's waving a towel.
Wow!
That's great!
I'm so happy.
How did Yamashita not get it?
Towel!
Did I wave a towel?
This is Shiraishi's.
That's why it's a "B".
Because it's Shiraishi.
It's similar.
This was easier to understand than the previous picture.
I'm glad.
You said it was good.
It's not as good as the other one, but...
Yamashita's super score is amazing.
That's for sure.
Yamashita took an overwhelming lead with his high-scoring practice.
The next question 5 starts with an English word clue
Slow.
Slow
Please write
Ah!
Here it comes.
Nice.
Yeah!
Yes!
That's great. You're slowly closing one side of your head.
Oh, my God, that feels good.
I got one. Nice.
This feels good. I'm glad to hear that.
You got one too?
I won!
I must've lost by pushing. That's frustrating.
This is huge. I got 10 and I didn't.
I don't want you to go away again.
Don't be so sad.
Don't say that.
I want him gone.
But what's the matter? It's incredibly interesting.
It feels good to be able to answer.
Bananaman did a great job.
The battle goes into the second half of the heated introductory round!
Today, we will announce the selected members for the 32nd single of Nogizaka46!
Every time a new single is released
the members who will perform the song will be selected.
Nogizaka46
Here is the formation of the members this time
Double center lineup
First, Yuna Shibata (3rd row)
Suzuki The name called out was
Rika Sato
Rika Sato, a 4th term student, was selected for the first time
I've always loved and admired Nogizaka, and it's always been my dream to work with my seniors.
I was so disappointed that it didn't come true.
I know how it feels to not be selected.
I'll do my best to make it even better than before.
I'm so happy that you're watching me warmly.
I'll do my best. I hope you'll watch over me warmly.
Third row, followed by Saya Yumiki.Third row: Na Yumiki, Saya Kanagawa
Iwamoto, Renshika. Hayakawa, Seira.
Next to be called out was Yohki Maou.
Thank you for your hard work!
Iyoki was selected for the first time from the 5th term students.
I'm really happy because I've been longing for this place.
But I wondered if I would be out of place there.
Of course, I'm a newcomer, so I need my seniors to pull me along.
But that's not enough.
I don't think it's enough to have that kind of regulation.
I want to do my best at my own pace in my own way.
I will do my best.
The next person whose name was called was
Miku Ichinose
Ichinose, also a 5th term student, was selected for the first time.
I'm not sure why, but it's a big part of me.
I'm still at a different level from my seniors.
I want to be like them, but
I'm not at the same level as them.
I'm not at the same level as them, and I'm not sure if the fans will accept me.
I'm worried about whether the fans will accept me or not.
In the third month, the last person to be drowned was
Miyu Matsuo
Matsuo, a 4th term student, was selected for the first time
I didn't expect to be invited.
I was surprised most of all, to be honest.
During the last Under Live, I learned a lot about myself.
I was able to accept the parts of myself that I don't like from my seniors and classmates.
My seniors and classmates accepted me very much.
It was a period when I gained confidence.
I will never forget that feeling and gratitude.
I want to do my best.
Next, the second row
The first name called was
Sakura Kawasaki!
Kawasaki became the third 5th term student to be selected for the first time.
I didn't really expect to be called by name.
I had no memory of when I was called.
I don't even remember replying to the call.
I don't know what to think.
I really don't know what I'm capable of.
I don't know what I'm capable of yet.
I'm full of anxiety.
I'll do my best to be a person who is worthy of the
I want to do my best to be a person who is worthy of the selection.
Then, my name was called...
Satsuki Sugawara
5th term student Sugawara became a selected member for the first time.
I don't know what's going to happen yet.
I don't know what's going to happen.
I can't imagine what will happen.
I don't know what to do.
To clap
Even if it's just a little bit.
I've always wanted to be of help
I want to help as much as I can.
I just can't say anything else.
I can only say that I will do my best.
Second row: Ayaaki Tsuji
Mayu Tamura
Minari Umezawa
Yuki Yoda
And the last one in the second row was
Nagi Inoue
Inoue, a 5th term student, became a selected member for the first time.
It's hard for me to narrow it down to one emotion.
I've been working as an O term student for a year now.
I'm happy to see the result of my activities
I'm also very happy.
I am also happy to see how everyone around me is getting better and better at what they do.
Even though we all started out the same way
I can't comment well, I can't say funny things, I can't say what I want to say.
I can't comment well, I can't say anything interesting, and I've been wondering what I can do.
I want to find something I can show myself during this selection period.
I really want to find what I can show myself during this selection period.
The last one is Sakura Endo from the first row.
Haruka Kaki
And the centers for the 32nd single are
Mizuki Yamashita and Shiori Kubo!
Third term students Yamashita and Kubo will be the double center!
The feeling of disbelief is
It's a big feeling.
It was the place I had been aiming for, but
But I didn't know if it was the right thing to do.
For the past 6 years
I had been working with the feeling that I had to catch up with Yamashita.
This is the first time for me to be at the center.
I am very happy that it is Yamashita's honor.
It's a new Nogizaka again.
I hope to make this a single that will make people feel that this is also Nogizaka.
I'll do my best so that I don't have any regrets.
This is the first single since the death of the first generation
Since this is the first single after the passing of the first generation
I hope that we will stand in front of the audience and fly to various places like our seniors have done for us.
We have to stand in front of the audience and catch all the air that comes our way.
I feel that we have to make it a single that will carry Nogizaka on our backs just like our predecessors did.
I was really strong about it.
But last time I was so full of myself.
So this time, I'm going to do my best while doing my best for myself.This time, I'm going to do my best to do my own thing, and I'm going to do it right.
while also looking at the whole picture.
I want to make the new Nogizaka in a good shape
I would like to work with Kubo and myself to create a new Nogizaka in a good way.
Entering the new Nogizaka Award
What kind of flowers will bloom from the buds that have newly sprouted?
I can't come up with a title.
It has to have a title of the year
It's like a bait palace for piranhas when you make a mistake
Den-den-den-den-den-den-den...
Manatsu Akimoto's graduation commemorative photo book to be released on February 21
Yokohama Arena, live immediate sales venue purchase privilege is determined.
Tickets for watching the birthday live streaming are now on sale
KOBORIDO-Yokozuna, I'm going to draw lots!
Senburi Chan
Oh, I can do it!
I'll do it!
Oh, hey, how is it?
Nikka
Oh, I can't stand it!